export default data = [
  {
      question: "I sometimes take John's coat for my own, because the two of them look so _____",
      options: ["original","cheerful","curious","similar"],
      correct_option: "similar"
  },
  {
      question: "George at first had difficulty swimming across the pool, but he finally succeeded on his fourth _____",
      options: ["attempt","process","instance","display"],
      correct_option: "attempt"
  },
  {
      question: "Several motorists were _____ waiting for the light to change",
      options: ["impossibly","impracticably","importantly","impatiently"],
      correct_option: "impatiently"
  },
  {
      question: "Mary wrote a letter of _____ to the manufacturer after her new car broke down three times in the same week",
      options: ["complaint","repair","depression","madness"],
      correct_option: "complaint"
  },
  {
      question: "John's poor math score must have _____ him a lot, because he is not attending the class any more",
      options: ["expelled","discouraged","impressed","finished"],
      correct_option: "discouraged"
  },
  {
      question: "The issue of environmental protection has not received much attention until very _____",
      options: ["seriously","recently","amazingly","dangerously"],
      correct_option: "recently"
  },
  {
      question: "The old man could _____ swallow because his throat was too dry",
      options: ["actually","strictly","exactly","hardly"],
      correct_option: "hardly"
  },
  {
      question: "We are more than willing to _____ our ties with those countries that are friendly to us",
      options: ["appeal","strengthen","expect","connect"],
      correct_option: "strengthen"
  },
  {
      question: "The artist is famous for his genius and great _____",
      options: ["fragrance","originality","sculptor","therapy"],
      correct_option: "originality"
  },
  {
      question: "Although some things are _____ , they nevertheless exist",
      options: ["important","intelligible","invisible","interesting"],
      correct_option: "invisible"
  },
]
